[Music]
hello and welcome to the junkyard love
my friends today's recommendation before
the podcast gets going is in the form of
a book the author today is Emily
Fletcher her name's Emily Fletcher and
the name of her book is stress less
accomplished more meditation for
extraordinary performance I read this
one I think it's a pretty good it's
pretty cut-and-dry it's a little wordy
on the title but it's a pretty pretty
condensed version of meditation it'll
it'll get you to at least feel something
so if you've never really felt anything
in meditation you sit down you're like
well that's that was fun cool enjoyable
did 110 minutes now what you don't feel
nothing I think that this is a good one
to get you to go oh okay I feel I see
what's possible so feel free to check
her out of course on YouTube as well she
has some guided meditations on there as
well check out that book Stressless
accomplished more Emily Fletcher let's
get going with the podcast we got you
honest it's a great combo take care of
yourself subscribe follow share with
your friends like all that stuff
certainly helps let's go hey man I just
want to start this off I'm gonna point
out this thing right here Shane Lee
bought me this other the beautiful minds
inspire others I really like the phrase
beautiful minds
it's like floats around a lot and John
belly and obviously beautiful mind I
have it tattooed on the back of my neck
was that a song or an album it's just
kind of like their thing like they're
like he like says it a couple times like
Oh ad-lib it in his songs I think that
it's from a movie called beautiful minds
about John
- duh so I think that he is
schizophrenic okay and he was a
professor MIT Harvard one of these I
haven't watch them for a while but
essentially super-smart but he was
schizophrenic and the movies called
beautiful minds is basically about like
how he's still like valuable you know he
has like his issues he has his craziness
he has its differences but he's still
valuable and um it's a great movie she
definitely minds but so I want to start
out with that because I feel like our
conversations are always wonderful and
you definitely have a beautiful mind my
friend I appreciate that and I was very
excited to actually come here because
it's not often that you sit back and
you're like I'm gonna go somewhere and
I'm gonna have a very in-depth
conversation right now about lord knows
what and the thing is like I don't care
where the conversation goes I know
wherever it goes I'm gonna leave
enlightened I'm gonna leave in a
completely different standpoint and I
feel like that's the that's like the
epitome of a beautiful mind is
understanding that every situation you
get into is an opportunity to be
enlightened in a very new manner and
that's why a man was such a beautiful
mind has a reminder right there we were
two men beautiful minds ready to learn
some new things man we can say [__] on
here right cheers to that [__] yeah we
can cool [__] yeah yeah all right okay
okay so but we are going to dive into
the exploration we're gonna we're gonna
go into wherever it takes us for sure
but I do want to get a little bit about
you my friends you want to uh you want
to tell the listeners how you got your
beautiful mind like maybe a little bit
of your creator side a little bit of
what you do and how you got inspired to
start doing what you do we're having a
good time
oh yeah so I I'm kinetise the name
itself we'll talk about later where it
came from it's kind of important but I
make music
my main goal in life is to create a
platform where not only I have the
opportunity to say everything I want I
have an opportunity to change people's
minds with what I say so
like this I the way
I think has always been from a very
young age I look back and I I don't feel
like I ever had a huge mine shift in my
life I feel like for some reason I was
born in a way that I could consistently
understand a lot more than I should
understand at that point and the getting
into the music was almost like this is
something that I need to do because it's
my only option it's like it's the only
way that I can live the life that I want
to live and that's a position of having
a platform so I can say everything that
the world is scared to say like a
language that you felt that you could
understand exactly it was it was just
something that I consistently knew that
there's something people can't don't
notice that has always been at the back
of my mind always aimed and that's why I
got any music and I started writing
really emotional music um my first two
albums were sad boy season all around in
at this point I've gotten into a point
in my life where I'm a lot more
comfortable with with with the
understanding that I've always had of
this way of thinking and that it's
worked out for me for a reason so it
lost my train of thought more uh more or
less yeah so I just got to a point where
I understood that music is the way that
I can get everything that I want achieve
everything that I want and just I guess
breed the excellence that I've always
wanted to see out of myself
the I've been making music for let's say
at this point my first ever album came
out in 2014 that was a very very sad EP
that I put out mainly because it was my
first EP that's why I was sad it wasn't
like cry sad it was like cringe sad you
know I mean it's still online you can
find it it's called serendipity
the perfect mistake so that came out
then in 2000
19:16 i put out another album that one
was called past chasers which that one
I'm very proud of I put a lot of money
into which a lot of people don't realize
that if you can't do it yourself you got
to put down a lot of money to get it
done right so I spend a lot of money on
that album pass chasers came out and I
mean it's done pretty good we're working
on putting on a movie for it and
listening to all those songs you really
get to understand who I am and what kind
of the thing that I think about
consistently and I always have very
emotional music it's always really fun
and getting to just like the past stuff
that I wrote just because like I could
see where I was at that point and I can
feel that emotional over again mm-hmm
there's so powerful to be able to do
that and right now we're working on a
little bit of a new drop style I'm
putting out singles as opposed to albums
just because you know Russ's idea we're
put out a song week every single week
until you make it obviously I'm not
gonna do that but hey I don't know I as
a Russ fan I dude I was I'm just gonna
say I caught him back on Soundcloud days
I got into impossible bro like every
Friday it's like I knew there was gonna
be a new arrest record every Tuesday or
whatever the [__] it was I was listening
when he was coming oh I loved his [__] I
caught him it wasn't right at the very
beginning I wasn't like one of the og og
fans but like he had started doing that
though and I caught on to the wave and I
loved every song that he put out and it
got to be this thing where it's like
like I'm listening to his old [__]
during the week but like he stays fresh
when there's a new song every week to
listen to so it was good dude I love
that that's a good idea that's a that's
a good in it's good to stay to stay
afloat and stay true to yourself you
know it's like like okay I got a goal
that makes sense in this physical world
it makes sense out here it makes sense
money-wise makes sense fanbase wise but
it also keeps me true keeps me not lazy
it keeps me working on my [__] you know
so even if it's not a beat a week or a
song a week like just keeping that
consistency of working on it and putting
[__] out yeah and that's that's kind of
the thing that rusts figured out before
a lot of other people did out at the
beginning it
really matters more about quantity than
it does about quality quality is
important because you don't want to look
back at your catalog later and be like
this is all the wackest thing I've ever
done in my life you more or less you
want to create good music but you need
to put out a lot because someone's gonna
listen to one good song that you put out
what do they do from there where are
they gonna go from there they won't
check the other [__] out exactly so
that's why I need to create a catalogue
of a lot more music so I'm gonna be
moving from the album to album stand
point to a single - single stand point
so that's gonna be a lot of fun that's
the journey that I'm on right now we're
doing a lot of shows lately since we got
the whole team together I'm on halflife
entertainment with Ryan Reed max V pain
which max B pain was on here I believe
two weeks ago or something like that
absolutely his it'll be okay soon and
then I believe that Ryan's gonna try to
finish the schedule no he's he's already
booked I forget exactly what day but I
think he said the 19th 16 yes so the
whole team's gonna roll through here so
it's gonna be really awesome for
everyone to hear how different we are
yeah but but dude I that's why I love
having you guys on here because you guys
you guys think big picture so you're not
just trying to like capture yourself
into one little lane or like let's try
to ride this little wave of this thing
like you guys always have been doing
this you guys consistently been doing
this you guys consistently put your
heart and soul into it like I've been to
practices I beat for you guys a couple
times I been to the shows you when you
guys think when you're thinking about a
song you're also thinking about the
music video and what you guys can be
doing live and what's the crowd do it
while you're doing that life and what's
the what's the listener thinking about
us he's here in this part of the song
you want it your storytellers is what
you are absolutely and I I just enjoy
your storytelling and I think that
storytelling is important I think
storytelling is a form of leadership
that is or it it really is in with with
our thing it's like at this point I'm
also working on a it's more or less I
kind of want to call it a full-length
movie kind of want to desperately call
it a full-length movie because the last
put out past chasers I'm making a whole
story behind it we're gonna put out a
full production of me and we got an
amazing actress who decided to pull off
on moving to LA just so we can get this
movie shot and it's gonna be music
videos Connect interconnected storyline
more or less so and that's kind of thing
like you said we while we're making the
song we're thinking about what the video
is gonna be and it's just because we
know that we live in such a world that
you need the auditory you need the
visual you need the feeling you
everything and so that's why if you
don't dip into literally every avenue
you are not giving yourself the full the
full opportunity to be everything that
you can be because if you're missing out
on YouTube monetization if you're
missing out on Facebook Instagram
monetization right now the biggest thing
ever is tick tock and it's breakin my
heart because I really don't want to get
on there but I know I have to because
you need to you you need to be
everywhere and so these are these are
kind of things that we're thinking about
because it comes down to longevity I
know I'm not ready to be in Hollywood
right now or like in the big picture
right now I know I'm very happy that
it's taken me this long to get where I
am because when I get what I where I
want to get I'm gonna be ready for it
because a lot of people are too excited
and that work everyone's too excited to
just get there but the problem is when
you get there are you gonna be ready for
it
yeah bro we're just I'm went down the
driveway where shoot some hoops we're
just like bro like if somebody hands you
a million dollars like you're just gonna
blow it like you don't know what to do
with the million dollars right now you
ain't ready with ready for it exactly
you gotta be you gotta you gotta build
up the man that's ready to handle the
situations you think you're so ready for
that's it when you when you make a
million as opposed to are giving a
million you thought you know a better
what you have a better chance of keeping
and fulfill or creating more out of that
million now if you come up on a million
because of the lottery
you're probably gonna blow it on a bunch
of dumb [__] right that's the point it's
like if you get it too easily you're
gonna squander your opportunities and we
see a lot of artists in like big times
like what
they made it as younger kids we would
see they would be put in the spotlight
when they made mistakes and that's not
something that I want ever I like I'm
the type of person that I don't want
anybody knowing you need any me doing
anything stupid because I don't do
anything stupid I avoid it at all cost
because I know that everything that I do
is gonna affect me it's gonna affect
somebody else it's gonna affect people's
understanding of my vision and my brain
right so it's really yeah so it whoa it
comes down to to building yourself up to
it comes down to building yourself up to
be the person that is ready for the
things that you know you deserve
anything you've got to be willing to to
make sacrifices and in some times you
know a lot of a lot of young people have
to deal with [__] in the light of day
I'm good you on that like I mean like
there's a lot of like III no doubt like
seventeen year old kids like a little
pump and [__] like I no doubt judge them
and it's like man like I would hate if
the [__] that I was doing I was being
such a [__] boy at that age like and
older man like that would hate if all my
[__] was just blasted to the world it'd
be so much harder to deal with like I I
think not only I would probably attack
back you know in like some sort of weird
Donald Trump like [__] egotistical
thing sorry yeah
but like I don't know bro it's it seems
a little weird to like have your shift
last night I think I totally get what
you mean like you wanna you want to just
be like still working like you are very
understanding of the work that it takes
to put in all you boys in half of it and
you guys are always working you know
always like you got your head down like
it you're not not trying to be loud at
times when you're not trying to be loud
you're trying to learn through your
mistakes in private and trying to deal
with things and and not have to make it
more difficult to deal with it's a weird
world that we live in have to deal with
[__] like in public you know I feel like
what a lot of people do fail at in in
this industry in a lot of industries is
trying to create a trying to create
their
to gain a fast fanbase before they even
know their own brand hmm and that's one
thing that like the team has been
pushing on me lately is rough
I guess curating more to show everybody
what my brand is and that's the thing we
we all we're all pushing so hard to get
the same exact thing and that's why we
are all able to push back and sit back
and be like hey this is something that
you're falling short on this is some
things that people don't even know about
so let's go ahead and fix this before it
becomes something that's gonna be a
problem and so if you're like you said
pump on all the younger generation
that's going in and then they're making
all these mistakes all it's all blasted
all over the place and you yourself
you're like I could judge them but I
know that I've done some really stupid
stuff and if I would have been in their
position at that time I probably would
have gotten caught too and so it was
it's it's really been great to learn how
to do what I want to do and how to keep
my nose clean right because when you get
out there if if and when I am presented
with the opportunity to do something big
it's gonna be I'm I'm not gonna make a
fool out of myself right yeah you would
be ready for it responsible like we went
on tonight with Cassidy recently I'm
kind of shy now cloud sorry yeah we
don't know hey hit me up and tell me
about the story there with Cassidy uh
it's KGW I remember I'm on my Facebook
mo socials a lot of times I don't do too
much growing so meet me as a new
listener
gotcha so uh the last show that we did
during the Christmas season we did a
benefit show which I'm pretty sure max
talked about it was it was benefit show
where we basically every all the
proceeds went directly to Target and
Burlington Coat Factory and we went and
we just bawled out on like 2,000 dollars
worth of toys and we took it to this we
took it to a spot this foster care help
spot and so that was one of the things
that we were able to do with like with
with the power of our music and before
the show I feel like it may be a good
reason why we
made so much money off of this show is
because we had a connection with a
really awesome person from culture which
is a Mediterranean restaurant out in
Portland and she got us connected with
KGW tonight with Cassidy and so we were
able to go onto the actual show into
their studio right where they sit by the
nor the newscasters sit and everything
max Ryan all of them got pictures taken
I was just like at that point I was
going through my hair transition phase
because I've been trying to grow my hair
out I was going through my hair
transition to fail you see I'm trying to
go full Samson and ro I'm a sample you
saying man is bringing up later in your
life for sure because I feel it's
beautiful you really find out how much
you don't like people when you start
growing your hair no it looks terrible
but we're starting just shut up gosh
but yeah so tonight with Cassidy we were
on there and they kind of just talked
about the opportunity that we have to do
the show for the kids the foster kids
that we were able to do boxes of love
that's what it was that was a company
that we gave the toys to and she kind of
shattered the team out we were even able
to get rage for the Cure I don't know if
maybe that was one of them that you was
that the one that you DJed for you do I
never remember the names max and I had
this same debacle I was like yeah I did
that one you think you know I don't know
okay and I've done a couple yeah so the
rage for the cure max was able to make a
really cool video out of it and they
played it on live television on like the
woods 8 o'clock 7 o'clock news so in
your ideas as a musician not either
exactly it was a so these are things
that we because the second that we
decided like this might sound a little
like selfish I don't want it to come off
that way in any way shape or form but
the second that we decided to stop
taking money for ourselves from these
shows is a second that the opportunities
grew and we started making a lot more
money and able to put it back into the
community so the less money we took for
ourselves the more of a name we made for
ourselves the more people started to get
to know some more people showed up to
our shows and
it turned into a powerful weapon that
like we're not doing this for ourselves
we're doing we're using the power we
have to do good for the community right
and that just blasted us into a whole
nother respect well I think that it puts
you guys in somewhere where you you fit
in nicely like it shows is the
authenticity like the crowd can sense
when the people who are on stage are
really into like what they're talking
about like it's it's it's a real
connection it's something really cool in
its in its full circle man it's it's you
you come into alignment with those
things and like you said the
opportunities start just popping up more
I don't know seems like that [__]
happens bro I mean that's that's
something I've I've been noticeable
about that kind of stuff and with this
podcast like the opportunities of just
you know certain things I just they're
just popping it up even just following
something like I'm trying to give back
and trying to to use my spare time to
feel like to help people
have a mental health podcast you realize
the power of the networking that you get
on just podcasting alone like the amount
of people that you get to meet and the
idea is that like people talk about on
this podcast is like man like you've got
a lifetime of knowledge just off of this
podcast no I feel like I'm like [__] you
go ahead extol something like it's like
a little gateway I'm like it's like I
shouldn't tell anybody about it or
something but like you just get to like
you talk to awesome people and just just
suck on the tit of knowledge for free
from some enlightenment I know here we
are know it's it's it's really awesome
like yeah so the team is doing great
things and I myself have always just
like I've written from the perspective
I've lived in right so it's like if I'm
in a position where I'm like super like
I spent a lot of time being a hopeless
romantic and stuff like that because a
lot of people don't realize I'm being a
lot of people who are hopeless romantics
are just people who are I guess lonely
in a way and they're like oh I could
treat someone so wonderful like the idea
is that okay so that's like the idea of
romantic that's really like we can we
can avoid it as much as we want me and
my friend would talk about it way back
in the day my buddy Bogdan when we were
like 14 years old we're like dude I kind
of feel like I'm super
emotional about women and that's weird
and at that point neither was really
dating at all because we were both in
like strict Christian families and so it
would even from that point we were like
just like we have like this deeper
emotion this deeper I guess what not
love but like we feel these things
deeper for some reason did you feel like
you had to like like you couldn't like
say it out loud like act it out like it
felt wrong it feels absolutely wrong
when everyone's like you're a guy you're
supposed to feel this way you're
supposed to feel this way
from that point on we're like look we we
find so much connection with the emotion
that we feel and we like we could sit
and talk about the fact that we like a
girl and we're not talking about any man
or all we want to be like we want to
smash we want to do this we were we were
like I could see the future in this like
and that's kind of just like the emotion
that we were able to talk between each
other and so that was really cool to
have a man friend that we could talk and
that made her write crazy it's crazy
it's crazy that it's crazy if you think
about it it's crazy there we just keep
crazy in and up I mean the fact that
we're not a let you know it's normal to
like have to be like whispering to your
friend like you can we talk about
emotions you know and it's so normalized
to just be like no no we're men we don't
we don't talk about those things and you
have to grow up being a little confused
about it like what what do I do with
these things nobody taught me how to do
it why is it taboo you know it's and
it's it's kind of funny you know it's
realizing how how easily it can be not
taboo you know we could just have these
conversations we just talked about them
so you were talking about how your
lyrics were always influenced like by
this by like my being romantic your
emotion yeah yeah and uh it's like the
one thing that I've noticed recently is
I had a almost like a switch like my
life got happier but the emotion is
still there and the music but it's a
very different emotion it's a it's a
very less hopeless romantic less oh I
can be your everything it's more of a yo
if you get me you're lucky
[__] your lights confident we're gonna
have a happy life if you get me that's
that's kind of like it's more of that
ideology it's like the emotion has
changed I've become less of a hopeless
romantic and I don't want to offend
anyone who like swears by the hopeless
romantic life which I used to I was like
such a hopeless romantic it's crazy like
that's why I started talking about bog
because we both were super hopeless
romantics and but it's like we still I
got no judgement towards people who are
hopeless romantics but it you kind of
have to get out of that hopeless thing
you don't wanna be hopeless and anything
like oh man no this is the main judgment
you cocooned out of this thing man it
seems like it's it's something that's
giving you a little more confidence like
something that's like you've discovered
like now that you've really dealt with
it for a long time and felt like what it
is like to be like that you were able to
say I don't just sit with this like yeah
I have this it is a thing that was born
with yeah I don't have to sit with this
you know what was that there was an
analogy we were talking about earlier
you know like a lot of our issues
sometimes it seems like whatever they
are you know even physical pain
sometimes like me aches depression and
not knowing something or not being not
being good at something we we take them
as they're like handed to us like a
bowling ball all right like like life or
somebody or genetics or your bad
circumstance gives you this bowling ball
and then the rest of our life would
figure out how to live with carrying
this bowling ball and that's just we got
to carry this in sometimes we get more
bowling ball we gotta carry those two
but what I should be doing is we go oh
[__] how do I get rid of this bowling
ball how can I change my life to where
I'm not carrying this bowling ball you
know and so it seems like you cocooned
and you said like this isn't a bowling
ball that's helpless romantic thing like
no no it's made me in depth and made me
intuitive with my emotions and made me
made me understand things that I can now
communicate with this language this
music language to other people and it's
created it's starting to create a
beautiful path for you it seems like
that's for sure I'm excited for started
for the future your music too for sure
yeah I I had to jump into R&B because
like man before I even ever started
dating I fell in love seven times yeah
yeah like I was that kid all right wait
what's your what's your are
means bow like who did who got you into
R&B take me back oh this is gonna this
is wild we had a conversation about my
dad earlier there's not much that I
really attest to him about me today but
my love for R&B through and through my
dad yeah yeah now my dad was a
photographer and one time to make up for
something that he did he took a bunch of
pictures of my mom and then he basically
put it to the song hold up let me sing
it a little bit okay
trained me like rose give me room to
grow shown your light of love on me and
gave me a so I can breathe you open
doors are closed in a world where
everything goes
you gave me strength so I stand tall
with things bed of Earth just like a
rose remember that song no no I like it
uh yeah hey one like a rose
it might dad put that song on to the
pictures of my mom and I remember being
kid in watching the slideshow that my
dad made for my mom and I started crying
oh wow and I like I had to I had to
runway I was like why am i crying right
now and then I had to stand close enough
just so I could hear the song and that
song and then the other one unbreak my
heart say love me again that was the
next song like I'm like dad you're
hitting it with the real stuff she fell
in love obviously it was it works
whatever he was doing working the road
but that's kind of what built me into
the whole like love on being you
remember this moment it's a slide show
like it happened yesterday and this was
2003 maybe earlier in how old are you
now for this new 25 25 25 years old 25
so back then probably what I don't want
to do math right now years old yeah 6 7
8 years somewhere somewhere in a million
yeah we smoked a little bit of weed
don't get mad at us but we did yes so
that's math isn't added in
conversation it's a different structure
my brain exactly best know where the
funds that but yeah so that's kind of
what got me and to iron being it's
actually the first song that I was at
that I was ever able to put on Instagram
of me singing was that song like a rose
yeah and like that was the first time I
kind of got a reaction from people like
I've posted stuff on like Facebook and I
posted like snapchat stories not a lot
of people responded a lot I mean some
people some like lifelong fans literally
lifelong fans have been responding for a
long time but at that point it was
people were like yo this kid actually
does something right like my family hit
me up and they're like you have a really
good voice it's like no duh what do you
what do you think that mean well bros
long here's a thing that i I read this
reddit comment and something that like
you you guys have never [__] listen
to at all that you guys have never had
this thought in any of you especially
you you're not afraid to like let this
emotion out but this uh this reddit
comment was it was like advice for
rappers on reddit or something and like
the first thing was like like 95% of
y'all sound like your parents are
sleeping in the room next to you so you
can't quite be as loud as you wanna get
in like bro in like it was kind of a
mean thing you know clown and like if
you really think about there's a lot of
people who in it's not you know this
ain't even a clown and thing to be
honest it's it's a real it's really hard
to get up on a stage or get up to where
people are watching you and let your
guard down that much to where you can be
like here's an emotion through wailing
of my voice like it's actually pretty
like it's a very difficult thing for a
lot of people to do and and to be able
to like really let that guard completely
down and just say what you have to say
communicate your emotion say say the
lyrics whether they're yours or you've
written them or that or you're just
relaying I understand this musicians
emotions that he was saying for this
song and I can relay them I'm a middle
man for this for this cover here and I
mean it's it's a way that that man's
that man's like voice can can carry to a
whole new crowd of people it's [__]
wonderful so but it's it
it's something that I admire a lot of
you guys but especially human you could
just you know afraid to let it rip in
any show that I've ever done with you
guys it's it's you're ready you're ready
to open up you know absolutely that
[__] that lion's roar on the stage
man it's is important now let me ask you
a question if I could if I could
question when you get on stage do you
get nervous do you get any sort of
anxiety or like how is that you've
probably spent a lot more time on state
well tech maybe yeah I mean I have like
different versions of stages because a
lot of with my audio directing a nod to
an audio engineer stuff it's less like
all DJ for like walkins like imagine
when the doors open at the Oscars or
ceremony and the people like the doors
are open and like all the people are
finding their seats there's music
playing then that I do a lot of
situations like that like not not the
Oscars at lower level like so I do like
ctsos so it's essentially I'm kind of
like if people I can do a couple things
to get attention in these and it's like
14,000 people so if I do too much I get
a lot of attention they like notice that
I'm in the sound booth whatever so that
that's a weird kind of thing it's a
little bit different than being on a
stage where everybody's looking at me
and then I also have different areas
where I'm in the back doing the same
doing a lot of that so I'm not with that
at all or where I'm at like a wedding
where I'm not really supposed to be the
focus of attention so there's a lot of
what I'm getting at is there's different
anxiety levels for each of these [__]
things focus I'm kind of at a point now
where where I'm doing with a lot of
anxiety of like projecting myself like
to where it's like like so what you guys
are doing like where you're like
performing your art yeah I wrote this I
got you I'm having trouble with that
right now I'm having a lot of anxiety
around that but I'm also having a lot of
like I don't know that I enjoy being
onstage that much like I don't know that
I get the high as much when I first
started DJing there wasn't nervousness
it was I wanted to like show these
people what it like what this thing is
that I've been working on I was like I
think is super technical and cool and so
I just felt like I was in my zone but I
was also when I first art DJing the
first like
five years I was very popular and I
stayed in a popular group I got you and
so it's very well that's the thing is is
you're like you stay pretty confident
when everybody likes you but then you
start going to places where you're like
you know and I bombed plenty of times
like I have such tons of times like
where I didn't read the room right and I
was just like too into my own header
into my own cool guy nests where I'm
just like playing [__] dubstep in
9:30 at the bar something stupid you
know Black Betty turns on in the wrong
situation that lambda am i can a but
yeah so okay so essentially yeah I've
gone I go through many different layers
of anxiety and where I'm at now I do a
lot of like my alone time I'm very
content being [__] a real introvert
now I've always I feel like I've always
been like an introvert that's like stuck
trying to be an extrovert
so I was like give me down oh yeah and
it's as I was unable to wear that armor
and that's kind of like was a lot of
like my like you know sort of break down
where I'm just like I wanted to end my
life you know so but [__] routing it
back to the anxiety now I have it's it's
it's it's not so bad when it comes to
just like doing my job or it's like I'm
hired to be a DJ that can they go play
at this bar this club or whatever it is
or any of my like audio engineer jobs
and you have my audio director jobs
those are totally fine like where I make
money but like if it's like me
performing my own like I'm Kronos I'm
the headliner like I'm booked for this
that sort of thing I don't have much
confidence in because after that kinda
like I don't really know what I want to
present
I had like some study I had some stutter
the other night I plan on doing open mic
night first I had them doing poetry and
open mic night okay and I [__] I was
super confident leading up to it and I
knew there was anxiety back my head but
I'm like I feel tough though like I'm
ready to face that anxiety no problem I
got it this time around
yeah but [__] couple hours before I
man I crumbled then totally crumbled and
I ended up not even going look like I
would I got to a point where I was like
you know what just accept it like this
thing is just bugging you don't bring
your poetry book let's just go and hang
out your friends because it cut my home
for that to run of the thing and end up
yeah so anxiety and the [__] winning
I didn't even like leaving house then I
know this house was a total mess and
this was just a few weeks ago sometimes
it's really important to let it happen
though man sometimes you need to
understand that your body is not
sometimes you just can't right well you
need a mate sometimes you just need to
get yourself that mental health care
yeah I mean well in and I felt I
strangely felt like a lot softer the
next day I felt a lot like I know that's
less constricted I don't know I think I
I think I'd been carrying a lot more
anxiety than I thought I had been that
week about it and it was this stupid
little silly thing where it's like you
get up for ten minutes like I could have
gone up and read one poem and like given
a toast totally fine but like that was
like controlling my thoughts that whole
week as it turned out so but it's it
made me realize like how sometimes I
obsessively think about things like that
right and I need to justify why
excessively thinking about it and so I'm
like oh it's important this and if I if
I do this right and I work on this it'll
be this in my life and so I turned into
this accidental big thing when it comes
down to it when the event comes upon us
anxiety can just grab it and I go oh
your whole life planned that you were
planning with this night it's [__]
shake you so so yeah I don't know I
guess I'm a little over the place with
the anxiety but for the most part I
would say outside of like that that like
presenting your own personal thing
I've got anxiety like really I feel that
I gotcha you know reason I ask you is
because it like I was almost bread for
bread for that life
manal ah and it was like my mom was part
of the worship team she was a leader of
the worship team so I spent my whole
life watching her on on top singing my
dad was a truck driver so he was always
driving around America he was always so
yes meet new people sending us postcards
pictures so I kind of was born with
music a big part of my life and seeing
travel everywhere and some of that kind
of bread me Ford I feel like the
music industry and the thing is like
also I was I went to like my family was
super strict religious so we when you're
in church you're part of the place
you're part of the poem readings are
part of all of it right so from a young
age you're forced to be on stage doing
all this stuff you're forced to be a
know so you have no stage fright like
did you ever at all man I'm telling you
really at all it's so because of all
those times that I was supposed to do
that is funny because I remember the
first time I ever performed I I'm not
gonna call the homie out because he
probably listens to this podcast we were
in first or second grade I'm gonna call
him now is for since the second grade
Jacob Trotter we were in the same grade
same class Rose Valley Elementary School
whoo
bro but he's like hey dude why don't we
join the talent show and we just did
this Christmas show that we did this
like little toy trains song I don't
remember it anymore
but he was like what'd you do that song
and I'm like cool yeah let's do it
and then the day we have to do it he's
like nah dude I don't want to do it no
hitting me I'm like you're gonna make me
do this alone suicide no it was my poor
first grade heart man
I still like I pray that someone hears
this hits you up and like hey I have a
video from that day if you want it
because I really want to see what I look
like on that stage it was must have been
amazing so I'm like this little kid I go
on stage by myself my hands are in my
pockets I'm looking down the mic the
whole time I sing the whole thing dude
I'm I did the whole thing like I'd stats
out on stage did the whole thing looked
up and walked off the stage and that was
it that was the first time that was the
only time I ever had stage fright or
anxiety on the stage and then past that
I just like ruined you know that seems
like it if this were like a movie it
seems like that would be like the most
devastating moment ever my brother's
wanted it to devastate me they wanted it
to ruin me because they remember you
probably should have picked your nose a
little bit
come on but no it's just that kind of I
was just proud of myself for the fact
that I didn't give up I was like I was
like it wasn't even my plan I didn't
want to do this in the first place but
then I told this kid I'll do it and then
I was like well if you're gonna quit
someone has to do it so I did it right
and so that's kind of like I built up
and me this kind of confidence on stage
like I'm very so I got a lot of social
anxiety if I don't smoke weed in big
situations so but the second I get on
stage it doesn't matter if I'm high
drunk sober as whole hell I'm chilling
I'm happy I'm already conquered that
[__] dude I uh my senior year I'm
definitely not gonna call this girl out
because her boyfriend won't be happy
about that one
but I call this girl I hit her up I'm
like yo I I wrote a song about you you
should come to senior night choirs doing
a senior night and I get to do some
mm-hmm choir was doing senior night so
everyone can do their own songs they can
do whatever they want to do
everyone did cover so I'm like I'm gonna
do my own track that I just wrote so she
comes out I started off the whole show
by taking the mic off the actual stand
and smashing my tooth smashing my tooth
oh no everyone saw obviously I'm
chilling I'm like okay that was cool
whatever I still do it
I still do that everywhere there was no
blood I did not break my luckily I did
not get screwed up but no so like I just
even after embarrassing myself like that
I just kind of killed it on stage came
down she's like haha actually it was fun
I enjoyed that a lot we don't talk about
that anymore but yeah so I've never had
that anxiety I kind of used this stage
to like build my confidence consistently
like I have the hardest time in my life
until the show comes up and I'm like
cool and the crazy thing is I've been
changing my act on stage I've been doing
crazier [__] I've been basically I've
hit the point in my career where I'm
like people know what your songs sound
like people know that you can sing
people will hear your song and then be
like he's a really good singer so care
less about what the hell you sound like
not a show and have fun do you know cuz
the second your energy starts blasting
throughout the whole stage everybody's
in and I think this stage like is my mo
comfortable spot but when I'm performing
the stages everywhere where do I want to
be yeah we just go crazy and like this
only has started happening the last
couple shows and my buddies have been
talking to me that like dude your
Energy's like through the roof it's
completely changed and I keep telling
him it's because I got the Sampson here
now yeah I'm feeling cocky oh yeah dude
so I got my times where I just feel I
just feel just chunky-monkey confident
man I just feel great but I have some
times where it sucks because I'm so
aware that like even as a DJ man like
I'm I've never been I mean I guess
there's been a few hip-hop shows where
I've I've been like amp and the crowd up
like running around with the mic that
sort of thing but outside of those few
times for the most part I'm kind of like
I'm mixing more than anything but I'm
jamming enough to where the crowd is
like feeling it like I'm dancing around
like cuz I'm just working you know I
understand just as much that dance down
here where no this is just what I do but
due to anxiety did definitely start to
get me to where like [__] man I wasn't
even like having a good time up there
and I went up there and I started to
hate the songs and then yeah man it's it
sucks but I have most of that I feel
like under control but it does suck when
it does like creep up on me it's anxiety
is such a [__] because so I actually
grew up a fairly confident dude it was
like a lot of it was like kind of mask
armor I kind of had to be based off of
that bring him but I I was a theater kid
too like I was in plays I was in the
talent show I danced to disco inferno by
50 cent I think it'd be 50 cent is it
lloyd banks or banks it was like it
literally said with my hand banging up
who dressed like oh yeah disco inferno
it's if I can hit but anyway that was
like seventh graders yeah yeah and then
like dude I never had to deal with any
of that [__] and I was like super good
at selling I was like oh when I was 16 I
[__] had multiple jobs was good at
people all that [__] and then
she had to started babbling up like I
don't know if it was maybe like
compounded anxiety from like childhood
and then just like not I didn't enjoy my
job at warehouser
but started getting more and more
anxious man wasn't able to really
perform now it's re not even like
bobbing my head much when I'm on stage
and then it starts making me like you
can't really [__] perform when you're
not even having a rhythm yeah
like and so I'm just like not really
having a smooth flow with a lot of what
I've been playing you know I like that
you brought up the whole dance thing
because I when I was 1516 I was part of
my church's dance team yeah and like
it's wild because our church did a dance
but like the songs that they used was
all weekend Park music hell yeah so it
was it was kind of like a story about a
lady being saved more or less but we had
actual dancers who have been
breakdancing for years and stuff like
that
and there was a point where they asked
all the youth are like do you want to be
a part of anything in the church and
there was the option of being in the
dance team and so I joined the dance
team and we like we created such a cool
dance that like we traveled around elect
six or seven churches and this like
Seattle California doing all those like
doing the dance and stuff like that so
that was really cool okay so when you
remember the dancer and I ain't gonna do
it no I do not man I wish I could I wish
I was what is it like like was it was it
like a hip-hop based dance or do you
remember it was it yeah it was him it
started off she was in a beautiful white
dress and she she was basically doing
not ballroom dancing not ballerina but
like nice little mix I'm just a
beautiful dances and then it was Lincoln
Park playing like during this you know
this part there was a beautiful song
playing some sweet and then all of a
sudden the lights in the church turned
red okay demons walked out right and
that's gonna be us we're just wearing
like black hoodies with black face like
black mark for like football marks on
her face right like we're gonna go play
a game of football or some dumb [__]
that for this boys and then the the idea
was that like the demons tainted her
white clothing and so I throw gloves
obviously we're not rubbing someone up
on stage and church like yeah so it was
just it was that kind of idea and then
Jesus comes and saves her and stuff like
that but we I was a demon and so it was
just like this really cool dance I
didn't have any gloves on that marked or
I didn't touch her at all because that
was not my job I wasn't the Glover
but it was kind of like it was pretty
hip-hop
it was pretty hip-hop from the demon
perspective and so that was really fun
to get into and that's why my senior
year I took hip-hop aerobics and that
was a mistake because I took it in Celso
high school you took hip-hop aerobics
that's crazy I mean as Cooley you guys
told that story in that way yeah I think
that's that's super cool I think that
like any organization should always
search for and like strive for some sort
of creative new way whether it may seem
on the fringes or strange at first
creative new ways to like explore and
teach people new things like look at
like now like your life here that's like
a genuine moment that you remember only
a part of you know oh yes probably same
thing the people in the audience know
definitely life-changing and yes so the
and that's another thing is like even
things that I wasn't professional that I
did on stage things that like I didn't
ever consider doing I did on stage and I
was not worried about it I've I don't
want to be an actor I've never wanted to
be an actor I'm super sketched out about
doing this movie because I'm the like on
the actor and so I like I've been
watching a lot of Heath Ledger lately I
don't know why but he's my inspiration
for acting boy but I get in try to
method act doesn't he do method acting
or he did do method acting oh you so but
I see that's the thing I don't know that
much about acting I just know that I
need to act my own story out hey don't
be afraid of looking into different ways
yeah and it's gonna be like I said about
my music it's gonna be a very emotional
movie it's gonna be it's the main goal
is to make people cry I want to make
people cry me and Ryan sat there and
we're like and we're like is this too
[__] up our people are gonna get
really pissed off because they're crying
through the whole entire thing or are we
like are we safe here like because
there's there's a lot of emotion in my
music there's a lot of motion in my life
and I'm not saying like I
get crazy emotional like I cry a lot I
get crazy I scream a lot it's just like
I've always understood emotion I've
always been accepting of the emotion
that I feel in a way that it doesn't
become detrimental that it doesn't come
out and act that I would be regretting
later on uh and so you know you yeah
it's channeled and it's not it's not cut
off I feel like a thing that people do
with their emotion is they completely
cut off their emotion because they don't
want to feel it and then it starts
building up and then when you finally
let that emotion in it's so deprecating
you can't get out you hit deep levels of
depression and I feel like a lot of the
reason why I've always been pretty
confident in my place on this earth and
wanting to stay on this earth is because
I've always been so accepting of the
emotion when it comes just so I can
understand why am I feeling like this
what's what's what does it mean for me
right right and then when you can learn
how to do that you get to a position
where you you're not scared to feel
these feelings you know you can get mad
and you know that you can control it
ma'am I'm gonna lie to you I'm not gonna
lie to you I'm gonna lie you know the
most embarrassing thing I've ever done
was put a hole in a wall like that's
such a kyle thing yeah okay all right
wait wait let's let's stop right here
though that's because let's say that
we've got people who have punched walls
and then they make me punch another wall
let's explain to them because sometimes
I think a lot of it they don't notice
they don't they don't notice that like
that's wrong they think like of course I
don't want a punch of all right but
there is some circumstances where
clearly I it's okay to get this mad like
they don't see it as like a wrongdoing
yeah we you know emotions and being you
know control your emotions like it
sounds like you took your hopeless
romanticism and you turn it into like
like harnessed romanticism and harnessed
ability to understand emotions because
of it you know I think how can we how
can we hang up there for people who
maybe still are punching walls what do
you think
so the thing man like it when that's it
when you let [__] Fester when you let
[__] build up for so long you're gonna
punch walls man you're gonna get so
stressed out with everything that's
tearing you down you're gonna start
punching walls so have you punched a
wall it's like because you got some [__]
festering man that time it was like I it
was more of oh man I can't talk about
this okay I got an open book
I cried my eyes out because like I was
having a stressful day the day before I
woke up stressed I couldn't find my keys
I was gonna be late to work and I was
worried about getting fired so I started
crying then I felt like I felt like I
was so out of control of my emotion that
I just turned around and punched a wall
right which is like it's the only time
it's ever happened it's the only time
it's ever going to happen but like it
was it was kind of one of those things
that everything built up and I wasn't
dealing with it I went to sleep I went
to sleep in a bad mood I went to sleep
had nightmares because I was in a bad
mood thinking about this situation all
day thinking about it all night and so
you wake up you punch a wall it's like I
feel like the best thing that you could
do for yourself is sit down in that
moment and and understand why am i mad
mmm why is this making me so angry is it
justified or is it just because there's
something else tearing me up inside
right now that I'm gonna take that and
I'm gonna push it on to another emotion
right I'm heartbroken I don't want
people to know that I'm hurt so I'm
gonna act out of aggression so people
don't think I'm hurt they just think I'm
mad right and that's kind of I feel like
the second that you learn to accept
those emotions and to let them do their
part they're there for a reason it's
it's one of the best gifts that we were
given to understand who we are yeah it's
telling you about the symptoms it's
telling you who I am why why this makes
me tick this makes me do this this makes
me do that but we're so afraid of it why
is this making me mad well a lot of the
times I think that we get stuck with
that like that you know holding this
bowling ball like okay I'm just someone
who punches walls it's just how do you
expect me to change what are you talking
about that's just what I do like they
don't feel like they're in control
like it's something that we think we
can't change Mike so I feel like we're
both pretty like in touch with our
emotions kind of guys okay I was saying
that I did though I had an experience
where I punched a dashboard I had with
with an ex-girlfriend years and years
ago and I was like 17 or 18 I punched
the dashboard yeah and I was I remember
when a half an ounce of what the [__]
that's not me like it was like I'm not
an external like I was I was more of the
like internalize all of my exactly
whatever you know and I remember doing
it but it's like you get to these things
and it's like you do and you hit the
dash and put the heck I didn't know that
was going on but what what that is
that's some [__] coming from your
subconscious kind of you know that's
some [__] that you're not in control
it's like it's hitting that button just
find that button it's pushing only that
button and that that's an area where
when you act out emotionally a punch a
wall you do those that's like like
you're saying it's it's showing you it's
pointing out like that it's where you
need to heal there's what you need to
work on stuff and your life does get
better when you met when you don't
accept that you you you don't have to be
hitting walls all the time you don't
have to be punching or acting out in
anger or or let up allowing your
emotions to grapple you and grab you and
make you make decisions that you don't
want to really make you realize you can
handle those it's it's empowering you
know there's its ways and you can you
can quote this next thing that I'm gonna
say quote you can definitely quote it
your subconscious is built off of regret
regression repression everything that
you repress like everything that you
hold back it goes somewhere it doesn't
just go away it goes into your
subconscious and all that repression it
more or less starts building like I said
the festering up inside you and then
your subconscious starts meeting I guess
screaming out for help right throwing
things out and you're like why would I
act in this way and that's so the
subconscious is pretty much built off of
repression everything that you've ever
repressed and so the best way to get
yourself to a point where you're no
longer letting your emotion take you out
of your own mind is understanding that
every time that you push something back
is just gonna build up the ceiling gets
hard higher and higher and higher until
it snaps yeah you got you got to take
these things sometimes you can take them
and like all right let it come out on
two out of your arm onto your fingers
and into a pen
onto a piece of paper you know like
write this thing that said of
suppressing and pushing it down and like
feeling the saying like well how do I
feel this thing's write it down take
your phone out write a note like why am
I feeling sayin just have a conversation
with yourself you know me and this wall
that's how I started i sat there
crisscross applesauce I was like the
[__] is going on man I started the
scientific method I took those things
that I was suppressing like these like
sadnesses adda fell for my childhood
that I just wasn't dealing with didn't
want to talk about but they were
affecting my future yeah you know they
were coming up and I just kept pushing
him down and then I kept you know
finding you know ways to numb them when
waste and run from them and at some
point you gotta be like all right let's
pull this thing out of me one by one
write it down or jot it down somewhere
talk to yourself have a conversation
figure it out yeah a lot of people it's
like everyone in every aspect you talk
to people about relationships in general
talking about friendships families
girlfriends boyfriends and you ask
what's the most important thing it's
communication you get into business with
somebody a partner what's the best thing
in the world for that business
communication now if in every aspect of
life communication is the best possible
thing but we completely neglect to
communicate with ourselves we completely
neglect to tell ourselves exactly what
we're feeling in letting ourselves
understand it it's okay that I'm feeling
like this it's okay that I'm sad as all
hell it's okay that I'm pissed off that
this happened yeah I need what it
happened yeah that's fine
yeah that doesn't make me a piece of
[__] just because I'm not happy all the
time
in the second that you start
understanding that you're building
yourself a stronger foundation for I
guess less aggression in the future you
can say yeah that's true and just being
able to hand the handle the abstract
emotions mmm yeah man it's very
important for us to realize that we can
handle the hard emotions like we have
such a our culture our society is so
seeking of comfort all the time you know
we're always like like that's the
ultimate goal is like being comfortable
and so the second that something that
comes up the second that an
uncomfortable feeling happens we pick up
our phone or we say something or we you
know break the silence or we we have to
run away from it or or do something to
escape the
things that are coming up but no being
able to cope with those things and being
able to take a look at them in
understanding that you can and you're
worthy of taking a look at them and your
life's worth you have getting better
wherever you're at you know I think
absolutely and yeah it's it's
communicate with yourself man tell
yourself yourself man I am okay I'm I'm
depressed
yeah I hate everything that's going on
right now that's fine that's fine
so let's sit down in this bed and play
some what are what's the new popular
game these days mattress 65
we're sponsored by best feed would be
nice but no so you sit there play your
video games for a day that's fine
tailor time because if you neglect to
give yourself the opportunity to
understand why you're feeling these
things you're like I said earlier you're
giving up on the best gift that you
possibly have to truly know who you are
as a person our emotions aren't there to
help us understand what our limits are
what ours we're all whole being is we
learned we through through joy and
happiness we learn what love is right
through anger we learn limits we learn
what we do and do not want to accept in
our life near our edges with depression
we with sadness you really delve into
how far you can make it as a human and
still make it back up like how far down
you can get and still bring yourself
back up so it shows you the power in
yourself so every emotion that you have
is built to build you up and if you're
always repressing it you're I feel like
you're mentally stunting yourself
emotionally mentally all of it what if
what if depression is just a signal from
your future self saying hey man you need
a reason to be stronger than you are
right now so I gotta give you some pain
I gotta sign you some pain I'm so sorry
I'm sorry but this is me your future
self I got to give you this pain like
you got to go through it because I'm
gonna need you to be strong I'm need us
to be strong later you know because I
wasn't I won't be able to handle it
yeah if you know if you can't handle
that I'll never be able to handle this
part in my life yeah
like like I need you I need you past
self like what if you what if you
thought about like when you're sad when
you're going through these tough times
what if it's like you know let yourself
feel these feelings you know let
yourself feel the real human emotions
but when it's time to to move forward
say alright you know what maybe this is
a gift from my future self saying we
gotta prep for some [__] so it's time to
make life a little better
exactly now and I mean I can honestly
say that I was very privileged in having
a mother who who was very very she had a
vast array of emotion she wasn't bipolar
or anything she was just a foreign mom
living in America raising three boys by
herself so you saw the whole spectrum
and so I I saw with my mom I saw that a
lot of times that it was it was very
deprecating for her when she got mad a
lot when she got stressed a lot she
would need to take pills and I'm not
talking about I don't know what it's
called ningún cut or something like that
it's like heart medication because
something her heart she had heart issues
in the past and a lot of it was because
she was so scared to let her emotion out
or she had no one to share it with that
it would start to fester up in she would
go through four emotions in the span of
a three hour period did she not have
very many friends she had an amazing
friend it's just when you're going
through that and you're going through
that in a community of your your ex's
family cuz my dad's family lives in
Kelso Longview and there's like you've
probably met 17 passar check to find out
a lot of us out here it's it's scary and
just your mom yeah so my mom was pretty
much she raised the boys still in the
community of her exes family just
because she couldn't we were raised
around our cousins and stuff like that
so she couldn't take us away from there
right and so it was hard for her to
reach out to anybody because of course
from the beginning there was that bias
yeah she probably wanted to make sure
she's appearing to be tough and she's
got it under control which I'm sure she
did but of course once I come home what
right we'll all unfold in we're time I
earlier like you know just like a
woman's role in in culture especially in
Lake situation like that she's got to be
strong got to be the strongest one ever
like she can't show a falter you know
she's got to be strong for her boys
exactly there's a lot of weight that
that gets put on to it motherly figure
in our culture there's a lot of judgment
that's the worst part there's so much
judgment trying to do their [__] best
right right some kid throwing a tantrum
in a Walmart it's not because she's a
terrible parent it's because maybe at
this point she's had enough
the child's had enough hasn't slept in
fourth it was slept well in four days
because he's had a cold or something
like yeah even that's the thing you
never know but there's so much judgement
put on on mothers and how the boys are
raised and so yeah it really put a lot
of strain on her and so in the home I
would see the strain that it caused I
would see the emotion that she felt and
so I had I had a lot of time to sit back
and be able to decipher the emotion she
was feeling and decipher why she was
feeling the way she was feeling and that
built a lot built up a lot of empathy in
my life and another conversation we were
having earlier was a the talks of that
we didn't understand when we were
younger the potential that we had to
help somebody the potential that when
someone's in a bad state of mind they
came to us and they asked us for help
and even though you may have even if you
haven't may have never been in that
situation or maybe you did go through
that situation and so you had something
to say to them later on they tell you
they're like you you changed my life
right you you may have saved me you may
have completely changed my thinking you
may have done all that but we didn't
realize that we had that power so we
didn't harness that power for such a
long time until we grew up and then we
sat back and we were able to say you
know what I'm super proud of the empathy
that you have for the people around you
and the fact that you don't do it for
anybody you don't do it for yourself you
just do it because that is the lifestyle
that you want to breathe and if it ever
happens that I have a child that is the
only thing that I want him to truly take
from me absolutely that as a human being
on this planet empathy is something that
is so rare so why not be that that
person why not be that person and we
were having that conversation where just
like if we sat back and we're like wow
we have so
power to just change people's lives
right there was a lot more we could have
done which we're still here so a lot of
time to do well no I mean yeah in
grabbing that and like just just just
saying like okay like people you know if
people inevitably come to you like if
you're that you're the empath Fran
you're that you're the counselor friend
that there are pew takfir and you're
it's like a psychology friends no you're
the you're the person who like like with
me it's like it seems like I'm like the
friend that people are like of course
when it comes to like depression and
suicide they'll come to me in those
senses but it's also there's parts of me
that like I'm able to like they'll know
they'll allow me to say like what what
they need to hear they don't want to
really maybe face but what I'll tell me
maybe the truth like it and I'm not mean
about it of course because I just I
understand the human condition you know
but yeah dude empathy is so important in
this world sometimes they just need
someone to flip that switch they can't
do it themselves and so they come to you
because in there's some people in this
world which if you're like this I'm not
judging you in any way shape or form
there are those kind of people that are
kind of like here's the answer fix it do
it some people just can't do it like
that right some people need that extra
push some people need that extra help
some people need someone to say you know
what that's a good idea and you don't
need my approval but I think that you
would do great in that and in that
portion they can sit back and there can
be like well he's confident in me why
can't I be confident in myself just that
little spark sometimes he sees the he
gets excitement in his eye when he sees
what I have the potential to do so why
would I let the the the fear that I feel
holding me back from doing something
amazing very powerful yeah you know I
think everybody has that power to just
just believe in each other you know to
me like just just give that confidence
seed of like you can do this that little
push they need yeah and that's like they
I I told you earlier that I sent him
that question to my favorite YouTube
artist Timothy DeLaGhetto on his new
podcast and he answered my question and
it's like you sit back and they they
just took the time to help somebody out
mm-hmm
took the time to all not only help me
out but three different people with
three opposing views and they all had
amazing views to give and I just sat
back and I'm like they didn't have to
spend 20 minutes talking about it right
like what they didn't have to do that at
all but they did because they understood
that there was somebody out there who
had an issue in their life and they want
and just wanted they already knew the
answer I already knew the answer but I
guess I just kind of needed that
reassurance that I'm not doing something
stupid right well I mean it's kind of
like you say that you already kind of
knew the answer but like sometimes we
kind of know [__] we don't not a word it
we don't really know like what it means
that we know so like when you sent in
this question and they're like all right
we are question is it's from someone so
today and here's what it is and they
read it and then they start talking
about it it's kind of like taking a
thought that's only in your mind that's
only hitting around the very narrow head
cavity we have here you know like as
much as we think we know so much we
don't know [__] so big fact that bro so
it takes it electronically puts it in
this microphone you know and or your
question you typed it whenever it was
and then they're able to like bounce
your [__] thought your thing that
just seems like it makes sense in your
head they can throw it around themselves
and they can spit it right back to you
and now you have like different opinions
and so that's the thing about questions
when you're willing to like it's like
hey here's my situation when we open
here's what's going on in my head what
do you guys think about it I think I
think it's an important thing to note
you're good at being on the receiving
side of things - yeah yeah you know a
lot of this a lot of this
self-improvement a lot of the stuff I'm
just like seeing your emotions and
seeing like whe your problems and being
able to step out from the outside
perspective is is being able to accept
you know not just feedback but accept
not exactly what you expected I suppose
- oh one phrase that I love this might
kind of tie in to what you were saying a
little bit it might be a little off
kilter but is that a word off-kilter is
now baby nice what if it all turns out
better than you expected
just think
every time what if it all ends up better
than you ever expected and every time I
get to a point where I'm like worried
about something about doing something
I'm just like so what if what what if it
turned out better than you think it's
going to and when you get to that point
you're like holy [__] it turned out a
million times better than over it that
would actually be a great exercise so
riding wise what if you have a panic
attack and you're like what if it made
to meet the open open mic night I'm like
what if I [__] up and what if I make a
fool of myself and what if I pee my
pants or whatever I was English like
like instead of you write down piece of
paper like what if it all works out
exactly how I want it to what if it all
goes great like and you start actually
answering yourself that could be a great
thing for anxiety
yeah and I just love that statement what
if it turns out better better better
better better than ever expect it better
than ever expect because that's the
thing man we get into the stuff and
we're doing the stuff that we're so like
we get a lot of anxiety about because we
put our heart into our art and so you're
you're almost like you're connecting
your emotion to that piece so if it
comes back in a way that's not
pleasurable it hurts it destroys you
but yeah it's like the one if you just
sit back and you're like look I did a
good job I did a good job in my view a
lot of people in this world will have my
view a lot of people will not and so
it's just like put it out there do it
and then see what happens and then every
time if you ask yourself every time
before what if it ends what if it goal
comes out better than expected you're
starting on a position where you want to
do more so it does end up better right
it's almost a reinforced elf look it
could be a lot better so you're already
starting this day off with the
expectation that you're gonna do a
little more just so it can be that much
better right so not only is it a good
way to get out of your head on it it's
also a good way to call the action push
yourself forward right
take
take that anxiety and use it to build up
whatever you were doing in the first
place and that's what's happened with
the last six shows that we've done as a
team like we've expected nothing but
like okay but it all comes out so much
better than I ever expected and the
thing is we did a show recently in a
Lincoln City there was not a lot of
people there but it was my favorite
performance to this day I had so much
fun I liked it city dude I just it was
it was a tiny bar the only people that
were there were locals and the artists
that were performing and I just let
myself unwind and go crazy or [__] and
it was the most beautiful thing I've
like that's the most beautiful feeling
I've ever had where I was like I let
everything go I was like let the emotion
that is in the song I'm singing I'm
putting it out to you so you can feel
and see exactly what I'm going through I
didn't cry on stage sadly that would
been really cool probably a good
monetization scheme but we'll think
about that later but no it's then
monetizing my tears beautiful it works
every day yeah you know what would
happen though is your to appear that you
would be that guy this is what you decry
and then you'd be like him and it's not
true I can't actually cry I'm losing
money I can't wait tears cry cry right
now
cry about all the money you're gonna
lose ya know full circle oh my goodness
ya know so it's um and it's a good life
it's a beautiful life yeah it's you're
in like I said understanding that the
emotion that you're feeling is gonna
actually benefit especially if you're in
the arts if you're doing something in
acting if you're doing something a lot
of the things that we go through do
create who we are as people but they can
also be really good a really good amuse
really good news for anything that you
want to create B paintings be acting be
a writing man I want to I want to start
hanging out with a lot more like
screenwriters and directors just cuz I
don't want to get into it but I want to
hang out with more of them I just want
to get to know what like what goes in
their mind that they can sit there for
four hours and write out a whole movie
in four hours and then create it I just
I just want to sit down and talk to them
you know
yeah it's like it's you if you're in the
arts it's it's a really good way to just
like take from experience and
if you've already sat there and let that
emotion and understood that emotion
you're able to paint that picture a lot
better because that's what I mean that's
what art that's what the arts are right
is communicating emotion in a different
just how music is a different language
than speaking there's whatever it may be
you know art all of the Arts is just a
generalized different way to express
human feelings yeah oh sure yeah you
know that's really all it is it's a
[__] beautiful way that we're able to
have like directors expressing in this
woman artist with a paintbrush and dudes
with [__] blowing glass and this guy
makes kites and this guy makes it like
we can express the depths of like human
beauty oh and those those videos on
Facebook those uh
couples dancing like those super
emotional couple dances where like
they're performing in front of their
whole like dance crew or whatever right
right right
you know those like those are my
favorite you know a lot of people love
watching like cat videos people love
watching dog you know some people like
watching like family returning home from
the military which is all beautiful but
I love watching those people dancing to
the most emotional music just like so
grow me to I'm I'm a chained to a dancer
Shay leads the dancers oh really yes
she's when we first got together she was
she was very heavy into dance and dude I
love that Shay have you seen it's I
think his name is
oh it's been Platt grow as we go is the
name of the song listener if you're
hearing this Ben Pratt
I think it's Platt right I don't know
[__] grow as we go but it's a wonderful
it's a piece like that where it's it's a
music video piece but it's to a guy and
a girl dancing and they do and it's you
know like it just accompanies with the
lyrics so well like you understand what
it's being said you know it's it's no
it's no conversation like you know they
don't say here's what this song is about
bah bah bah bah bah bah bah you know and
they don't have to write that on the
screen it's just the guy singing the
song and in the dancers dancing the
dance and you just listen and you watch
and you're like I know what's happening
there and it's just like yeah it's like
that's actually something that
I really want to do for michaux dyou one
of the songs that I got coming out her
throwing the more emotional one I want
to do a video like that so if anybody is
a dance choreographer and has I need two
male dancers and one lady dancer and if
you want to be part of a music video you
should hit me up because we're gonna
create the most emotional beautiful like
it's basically gonna be a music video so
like you're gonna say it's like movie
style you're gonna see what's happening
in real life and then it's gonna switch
over to the dance world and they're
pretty much gonna be like interpreting
what's happening through dance I hope
nothing more than to start some
conversations that start with hey I
heard you say this thing on Jake's
podcast I'm such as such like I want to
make that happen so creators definitely
reach out can you give you're at real
quick just we don't forget this so you
can get me on Instagram snapchat of
Facebook at K a and I de is and that's
gonna be on pretty much all platforms
Yanis can itis on Facebook so if you hit
me up and you're willing to get to work
right now just for another video I I've
been hitting up my buddies and I'm like
hey I need some skaters for this video
just because I want to like show off the
people that I have in my life the people
that like I knew in high school the
people that like I was always jealous of
for some reason I want to bring them
into my music and videos so I got four
skaters and we're gonna be doing this
really cool shoot at four to five
different skate parks so like that's the
thing man I'm just trying to find
another skater it's been a while you
skate though well that's that was so my
identity in high school was a skater
yeah dude I do need a skater because I
need someone who can act and fall in
love in the movie no I mean no I didn't
fall in love but you know no I do that
around here we don't do that I'm down
though that action that actually sounds
super fun though oh it's gonna talk
about that later on that's gonna be
perfect but ya know man right now is
just that's the goal I want to I got
emotional music but I want to portray
that emotion in really cool ways I
really do
and tell me in the the song that the
skaters are for it's such a teenaged
song like it probably gone
tick-tock very well but like so I want
to kind of give that vibe of like young
love of not only loving people but
loving what you do skating shredding and
stuff like that just going in it right
almost the look of like we broke into a
skate park in the middle of the night to
do this crazy [__] love it so you know
that's kind of all dude you guys think
full circle you think full circle you
think big picture you think long-term
you think like patients your patient man
breaks my heart because you want it all
to come out right away but you know it's
just building you're sitting there
you're totally like piece by piece by
piece the crazy thing is for that song
the only thing I have ready is the song
itself in the artwork for the track and
then now that means that I have to
create a lyric music video I got to
create a full-length music video we got
to go on promo I got to get a bunch
about like six videos and tik-tok so one
might start popping off on there so I
can fire throwing my music on it see
that's what I did on promotores hit me
up - yeah head tick-tock
dude that's the thing is it's crazy like
being a you know like I try to sway away
from social media myself but like you do
get it does come full circle like
constantly doing this thing is what
fills your life with I'm always getting
better at what I'm doing like me I was
talking earlier about how I make my you
know making my thumbnails and making my
just the album arts for stuff like
taking time to make those and not always
trying to like because when you don't
have the money for these things you got
to outsource it right so a lot of these
people in this podcasts are like we're
talking about or start people start now
and they're telling you like no no I
just had watched hours and hours and
hours and hours of YouTube and when we
learned how to do these things like that
seemed like my brother did that with
video editing and like I keep saying
like there's a bunch of deities on my
team it's a where we're living on Mount
Olympus like that's about it bro yeah
it's like because I'm where we were a
group of three people for a long time
was just me Max and Ryan max is my
brother Ryan is his best friend max
didn't want me joining the team so I
went around his back and talked to his
buddy Ryan
and he was like hell yeah
and now Max is very happy that that
happened but now we're just we're
bringing in people finally after like
eight years of doing this six years 2012
to 2020 eight years we finally brought
on three more people and that was that
was just something that we finally found
people who were riding the same wave
people who like at this point the crazy
thing is like I have all this planned
man I also have to plan around like
everybody else's schedule because we're
as a record label how we're doing is we
want to keep us in your ear the whole
year right so buddy's dropping a song
next thing you know he's dropping an
album I'm dropping two tracks the next
guys dropping a music video half-life is
in your face it's good so that's kind of
what we're on but like I said earlier
just you kind of get like you kind of
get that's where I get anxiety like I
just want this to come out ready I want
people to see this I won't be ready like
it was really what I'm feeling really
like this this fit photo that I keep
showing you bro I'm so excited about it
like it's it was the stupidest little
thing ever but we sat there we laughed
our asses off for a deal man it's is the
deal it's a dope photo it's perfect for
tea I like it I like how it like notches
it down I always love like when it's
like like a you know even a more serious
part of a song or even like a more where
you like we're the album art you see it
you're like oh that's different than I
expected but now I
okay I think I do get this [__]
a little bit more you know you're always
trying to like as an artist every piece
that you come out with like whether
that's like with the promoting of it
with the actual piece with the
performance of it with the the lyrics
video with the everything associated
with it you're trying to paint a little
bit of a picture of what you kind of
meant and that's a little bit of I
couldn't think you are yeah piece of you
know so you're always trying to like
communicate as fully as you can but it's
[__] the interesting thing dude an
artist is like the most confusing person
to understand in every way but also
there are saying the most about
themselves so the person who's saying
like here's the here's the deepest parts
of my soul and I'm disguising them with
this sort of language and people like
yeah I love it
it's so beautiful don't understand you
at all yeah we know you know like Jesus
Christ Oh such a weird world but yeah I
do not date an artist do not do it do
you not date an artist you cannot do it
I mean Shaylee stuck with an artist
she's an artist herself so it works out
she's an artist she's she chose her art
through dances what you said which is
beautiful I need dancers I need
everything right now at this point we're
just like we're having fun with what
weird hill laughing yeah no no that's
dude I've been doing that to like a lot
of with because I'm getting a lot of
people who are up off the ground getting
buff again and we're gonna have like
some YouTube creator de [__] like that
stuff you know and then we've talking to
we'll get some musician days up here
just makes it to make some shitty [__]
make some good happens oh yeah we were
talking about that last year remember we
were like two years ago you right when
you were building your studio we were
talking on Instagram and you're like
yeah dude you should come over sometime
when I get my studio fixed up and then
we could just go crazy just join us and
so it's like when I showed up for that
last podcast I walked in here I'm like
yes this is the place that you just come
to release like just enjoy your damn
self it feels good it's a good
environment you walk in here and you
feel like this is exactly where I need
to be right now every time I feel that
way it's beautiful in there man
thanks man I appreciate that it's uh I
had my friend Jay over and she's in
she's like wow it's pretty intense to be
inside your mind and I was like oh yeah
that is true that I just exploded my
brain onto the wall but I you know I
take care of my mind now I love my mind
a little bit very much I love this room
and I love Mike I love being able to
offer a comfortable place where people
can come in here and like leave their
skin at the door and hang up their mask
and like just be their true real self
and whatever I can do to make them feel
that way it's it's something that like
is inherent and harun me like I've
always been like a host yeah you know
I've always worked live events and such
but it's cool to step into it and like
have it it's not like I'm like trying
that hard I'm just like making it be
authentically me down here like this is
what I love this is what's very
comfortable for me and what I would like
to have if I came over you know someone
else environment like thinking that way
so Justin I said it comes across
yeah man in like we're talking about
that TV earlier
you just like that makes me so happy I
have no idea why
like just googly eyes on a TV crying and
the TV says I'm broken but I can be I
can still be used for art like that that
makes me happy and so I'm not gonna lie
to you yeah dude I think it was so I
think the moment it happened when I
wrote it so I told you I I drew this I
painted the face on it afterwards that
was an afterthought uh-huh that's
probably a year after the TV itself I
want to say that I had some like dorky
catastrophe where I where I had dropped
it and I was bummed about it and some
what I was trying to be like dude let's
be positive and so I I put it in front
of the chimney like tastefully liked
where it covered up the perfect the
front end there yeah and then but I'm
broken mike is still the user and I set
it there and I was like that's on
purpose you know so instead of it being
like this broken thing I turned into
really I love that because man how long
ago was it that that broke it's been
probably two years they're probably a
pretty expensive TV when you got it
yeah I feel like to be honest Shaylee
probably purchased that TV yeah like
yeah and a lot of times probably
expensive as hell when we first got it
cuz those for a while those with like
600 noise people just get directly in a
negative and I love that you said that
because you just took that and you're
like hey let's stay positive let's do
something fun with it and that's why I
like yes I'm sitting here and I'm like
dude I would almost kind of turn on the
TV if it was possible just so you could
see it's broken but that's written right
on it and you're just like it's almost
like it's reused for a happiness yeah
right it is dude you got to repurpose
[__] I mean it's the beauties in the eye
of the beholder
you got to see things differently a lot
of times your first initial reaction is
the sadness you know you dropped it you
TV falls off the wall you're like what
the [__] this sucks because insulae what
goes through your head is like I gotta
buy a new and it cost this much and how
much I pay for this you know but you got
a that situation is going to happen what
happens next
is gonna happen regardless if you keep
that I'm pissed off enough so if you can
just throw in some sort of fun for your
life right and right in the middle of
that you stop yourself right into tracks
and eventually if you keep doing it your
life just your initial reaction is not
even really like you know I feel like
more and more you know things happen and
sometimes they're just instantly
silly to me that's just life reminded me
about being one more careful where I
wants my TV yeah and I mean with just
kind of like we've been talking about
this whole time that's the emotional
enlightenment you've sat back and you're
like why am i mad right now what am I
gonna do about it and you're like I'm
gonna put some googly eyes on it and
then draw a Sun row you ever put googly
eyes on [__] though it's exciting yo
what are you gonna do to people in your
life it's don't tell them you have
googly eyes but you start putting it on
stuff like discreetly like do like two
things in your home at a time and then
like nobody will say anything Mike
because they'll like snicker at it but
not interact with it and then you got to
put more things and then eventually if
you want to put stuff on Mike in the
fridge they'll definitely notice but
there's things in this house that have
googly eyes there's things that Megan
Elam owns that still has googly eyes
probably I think that I put googly eyes
on my sister's car at one point they
just make people laugh the googly eyes
heard there are like bro whoopee
cushions what the [__] happened to that
really like when was the last time you
saw one of those he ever do pranks when
you were growing up like were you prank
her at all yeah but it was like me and
my brothers so it was like a little
screwed up like [__] don't you just be
an [__] yeah you're just like it's
not even funny it's just screwed up
you're like why the hell would you do
that [__] yeah whatever
we we threw a cat off a bridge and so
you know it was with such a pranksters
like we were those kids that like dude
we're so stupid we thought it would be
funny to throw rocks at cars while they
were driving by no I've done that for
students so so much great you know I
used to do airsoft guns like oh my god
we used to shoot crackheads and then a
laser pointers I swear to you there'd be
where I had lived where there was so
many Krakens on bikes we would try to
get the crackheads we we just refer to
these people as crackheads crazy
so you're Dickens what if we were to
shine a laser light in their eye this is
my upbringing Jesus it's so crazy like
this [__] that you did wouldn't you wear
a little [__] dude it's crazy to see it
come full circle to cuz we like it was a
while ago actually this happened
probably a year and a half ago I was
driving down the road and I was driving
through Portland mean you know in
Portland under a lot of bridges it's
legal to set up tents and [__] there's
kids cut in class bare macing a bum oh
my gosh
it was unreal and it was a cloud dude it
wasn't like pepper spray it was bear
mace it was like a big-ass can't a in
there no I think they were just having
fun that's so crazy dude like these kids
like they're gonna they have no idea
that they're gonna have to grow up if I
remember this yeah bro it's gonna be
either way it's goose you do what you
gotta do oh yeah there it is no yeah
well swipe it off afterwards all right
bro hey I have a question that so I've
been trying what I've been trying to do
is like when I have a random thought oh
my god let me a cool podcast question
just to ask like any guest at any time
you know like sometimes when you're like
ah what else do I want to talk about so
this question was when's the last time
that you changed your mind about
something and if you can think of
anything I'll give you a minute on that
if you can think of anything that you
changed your mind on like or you changed
your perspective
okay used to think this way and now I
think this way like I changed open
relationships relationships
relationships now I'm a serial
monogamist it's not something that I'll
ever like I don't think I'll ever want
to get into an open relationship but my
view of of an open relationship has
broadened and I think is the most
beautiful thing in the world really do
you think to the power of being able
having such good communication with
somebody in putting such a putting into
perspective that they're not doing this
to hurt me they're doing this for them
mm-hmm it's amazing especially because
you think about it we have one life on
this earth and we as people who get in
relationships pretty much put our
significant others into boxes yeah and
voluntary and sometimes you get in a
relationship with someone who's amazing
but they're polyamorous in you're
monogamous hmm now for you you have a
decision to make either cut them off
completely find someone new or talk
about an open relationship see if
something that that's something that
you're comfortable with and man I've
gotten like I've been listening to
podcast
Shambu T she's a sex that uh sex
specialist okay I know her I think I may
be seen a TED talk or something yeah
absolutely
yes she's she's a smart lady she's like
she was kind of talking about open
relationships and it's
over the past couple months it's just
it's a whole new world to me it's like
like I said I'm not a serial monogamist
I like the idea of hey one person in the
world who's for me I'm for them that's
beautiful that's what I want to do yeah
but to like anybody who wants to get in
an open relationship I'm like if you are
strong enough to do so I have so much
respect for you look for you so you
changed your mind on that exact home you
know I feel like I I changed my mind on
that too just listening to Aubree Marcus
he talks about that a lot
he's him in his ex-girlfriend or current
girlfriend I don't know they keep I
can't remember but but they had they had
an open relationship to it some of his
perspectives on it I was like wow I
didn't really think that I would change
my mind on that but it's interesting to
listen to people and change your mind
about it also that sparks this [__]
thing he just did I was listen to his
podcast this morning Aubree Marcus you
know that is I don't he co-owns I'm on
it with I think Joe Rogan owns like half
a door third of it but like Alpha grain
from on it they make like all kinds of
like workout supplements workout your
kettlebell tangible stuff but up yeah
I'll be mark has just got Noah the
darkness retreat bro yeah Oh what that
sounds scary darkness retreat so he's
he's a dude he's savage he's done he's
done like travel all around the the
world and done like ayahuasca ceremonies
and DMT ceremony you know like all these
[__] different like ceremonies and
like okay he explores him and he comes
back he has a podcast him talks about
he's great he's pretty into like just
exploring the human mind I feel like you
know post post military is it done guy
no no I don't think he's possibility I
mean he may be it could be it could be
off on that obvious either way I know he
kind of has that put in that military
vibe but I kind of savage but anyway he
did a darkness retreat and he was just
he was talking about like what you do is
you go it's like six or seven days and
you go and you have like a mind fold and
you're just in darkness for like like
you have a room so he said like the
first day just getting familiar with the
room yeah he's just like feeling it out
whatever there's a window you can open
the window but you have to have you like
mind fold like it's
full like head blindfold make sure no
light gets in you have to have that on
like anytime so it's like you don't ever
want to see any light for these seven
days like I think he had a way that
people even took him on walks we think
went on like small like walks and hikes
and stuff like oldie I don't know
exactly I didn't finish the whole
podcast but huh either way a [__]
darkness retreat and he said it was like
one of the most profound things
oh dude I would love to do that alright
imagine visual [__] like if you loosen
it absolutely exactly your mind is given
is your mind is forced to create imagery
for you right wait you know what's funny
is it's not forced to create imagery
it's not forced to hallucinate it's
almost like it gets rid of it it's like
a like a sculpture you get rid of the
clay that's not the sculpture it starts
to remove the pieces like it starts to
show you the everything that you truly
are oh yeah I think I think a lot of the
things that we have is as people the
abilities that we have could be holding
us back from learning a lot of things
and that's why I like meditation and the
idea of astral projection and things
like that it's like it's it's so it's so
profound and it's so like I believe it
100% because we are capable of so much
with our great minds that we just don't
let ourselves delve into we don't we
don't train ourselves in those things
and so honestly I'm not gonna lie to you
I think there is a very high possibility
that psychics oh for sure oh I like what
what do you think like what what when
you say psychics like what pops in your
mind like what do you think is like
probably happening like what like what
what's a level of psychics I'm talking
about legitimate this is gonna happen in
your life oh I don't know when I don't
know how but this is gonna happen in
your life [__] I truly believe you ever
been just thank you I have not I want I
think now one thing is I want to go to a
psychic really bad and I also really
want to go to a therapist really bad not
because I feel like I have any emotional
or mental issues that I needed um I just
want to get to know myself more you know
and I don't think there's a better way
to do that than to go through a
therapist who is trained to make you
open up parts of your mind I think you
can do that by yourself
yeah dude if you have a comfortable
environment and this is a place that's
been years and years of research of like
how do we make this person the most
comfortable that we can to allow them to
express you know what's going on with
them truly I mean it's the quicker you
can get comfortable in that environment
and with that person [__] yeah awesome
that's the sooner you can start to deal
and deal with things in your life that
maybe you wanted to deal with yeah and
those are other things in my life that
were a major change in my life that
beliefs starting to believe in things
like that and it's like I mean if you
want to think about it on a scientific
perspective what we're all made of atoms
and maybe there's some sort of deeper
connection between all of us in the
universe and so that I mean I'm that's
the thing like it's just to live in a
mind state where you're like no that's
impossible
that's never gonna happen no I don't
think that's possible at all why why is
that impossible man
why think about it like why not an open
relationship why not uh well I think
people directly put it on to their life
without thinking about other people's
life so they don't even allow themself
to explore into things very far like we
said people take things that isn't
really related to them and they take it
to heart and it's the they're forced to
show their own emotion over something
that's not even connected to them in any
way and that's one thing that I kind of
thought about open relationships is uh
one thing about an open relationship is
you realize that uh they're not doing
this action to hurt me they're doing
this because they need it for some
reason as a human because like I've told
all my friends I've told pretty much
everyone I talked to there are people
who are monogamous there are people who
are polyamorous polygamists I don't know
the difference sadly I should probably
learn but there's a big difference and I
think the best thing in the world that
we can do is sit back and understand
that there's more than just one way to
fall in love because at that point we're
hurting a lot less people because we're
not choosing the wrong people we're
opening up the communication lines and
so that's that's why I've been opened up
into like the whole idea of like the
open relationship and the fact that I do
this because it's something that I need
to do and it shouldn't hurt you it
shouldn't be it shouldn't cause you any
sort of her
motion because this is something in my
life but then again sex is very seen as
a very sacred thing and so of course
it's it's definitely kind of taboo in
that manner but like it also comes down
to just because you're in an open
relationship doesn't mean you're [__]
right it doesn't mean you're going out
and smashing anybody else the idea of an
open relationship is you're your own
human being I want you to do whatever
you want to do if it hurts me sadly I
might have to take my leave if not fine
we'll get over it just be open to me
communicate that to me tell me that
right help me understand why you need
what you need maybe we can build a
stronger relationship based off the fact
that I am NOT holding back what you need
right some people need sex because the
structure of how we live life is is like
given to us like here's here's how you
live life and this is right this is
wrong
yeah as you get older you learn like oh
okay like I don't have to take the
structure that everybody gave me I can
learn what works for me learn for works
for other people and you could explore
that it's interesting alright we are
getting up here in time and I do have to
pee but I do if there's anything you
want to add definitely add it but let's
start with if aliens came right now
you're in the backyard you're smoking
today my backyard I'm down here I'm
taking a piss you're just like waiting
for me [__] alien saucer comes down
backyard he says you know that's what
was good bro like what's like what what
are humans all about like what what are
you gonna say in what are you gonna say
to him he's like bro like give me a
reason a [__] reason no pressure
though bro look look I would I would
first of all try to reason with him and
help him understand that there are some
people on this world who are empaths
like us and it's it's mind-blowing that
someone could have so much love for
someone that has no connection to them
but really since we both know that's not
going to work the last twelve just do
the thing just I mean I don't want to
talk about politics but like if they
came down here right now that would be
very bad for America yeah we're we're
before our cocoon stage I think whatever
we're in the havok stage of just
eating a bunch of hot pockets before we
go into our cocoon stage and to build
our are smelly shitty hot pockets into
wings somehow we're eating the hot
pockets I think that's for the stage
that's the stage yeah I think that'll
explain to the aliens very well what's
going on yeah they're like damn hot
pockets that was like 12 million years
ago right [__] time to blow this [__]
off all right bro hey will you do me the
favor and you don't have to do this I'm
sorry I just put you two on the spot we
say like good night from the chick I
love podcasts where you seeing us out
from the junk I love podcasts me you got
like a jingle something you could think
of just a short little something let me
think of something simple or something
something whatever you want but it's
junkyard coming at you fast yeah it's
junky I love hold on let me try this is
good okay is junkyard O's coming at you
fast is junk hot [__] that up again I'll
try again is junkyard love coming at
your fastest junkyard love don't let the
moment pass with junkyard love Jake
Ryan's in the building baby we gonna
take this pony on now tonight oh it's
out oh yeah that's junk on this podcast
have a good night peace out
you